Feifei
Sister Feifei
Wu Ming
What's wrong with her?
It's nothing.
Just some shady little tricks.
I knew it.
Guess a junior like you isn't up to it.
This Mother-Child Gu
comes and goes without a trace.
It can also fuse with flesh and blood.
Not just anyone can force it out.
Boy.
You've lost.
If you kneel and kowtow to me now,
I might consider sparing your arm.
He lost,
but you didn't win either.
Want my brother-in-law to kneel to you?
Keep dreaming.
What?
In front of everyone,
you're trying to weasel out?
This wager
was something he agreed to himself.
So what if we do?
Why play fair with an old creep like you?
I accept my loss.
Wu Ming.
Brother Ming.
I'll handle this matter.
I can settle it.
I only said I'd accept my loss.
But when have I ever lost?
Boy,
you're in this deep,
and you're still talking tough?
Do you have any other tricks left?
Tricks?
I've got plenty.
Brother Ming,
what is this thing?
This...
My very soul is trembling.
Ghost Needle.
Gu-Devouring.
Master.
Impossible.
The Mother Gu was destroyed.
Absolutely impossible.
How did you do it?
Evil deeds bring their own ruin.
Raising Gu to harm others only harms you.
Boy,
do you think
a bit of skill lets you look down on me?
The victor is yet to be decided.
Die!
A Yi.
Are you okay?
I'll live.
Save them first.
Where's my sister?
Wu Ming.
Hurry, go save my sister.
She's carrying your child.
Please don't let anything happen to her.
Wu Ming.
Did you succeed just now?
Can my mom still be saved?
Eat this.
Feifei.
Mom.
Your leg is healed.
Sweetheart.
You've been through so much.
Mom.
Feifei.
You've been through a lot.
You.
Aren't you going to ask who I am?
Or why I brought you here?
If you want to talk,
you'll tell me.
You bringing me here
can't be anything good.
You do have some insight.
Right now, I
regret not refining you into a Mei sooner.
Letting Wu Ming have you so easily.
You're Guichen.
That's right.
And once known as Tian Yi.
But that's all in the past now.
You took me
to get to Wu Ming.
You want to use us to threaten him.
You are, in my carefully laid plan,
a very crucial piece on the board.
I've nurtured you for so long,
but hadn't had the chance to pluck you.
A pity, indeed,
but I can use your body
to break Wu Ming's Primordial Yang,
damage his Cultivation Base,
which counts as a small reward.
What I didn't expect
is that from just one time,
you'd be carrying his cursed offspring.
That truly is
an unexpected delight.
Wu Ming is heartless and cold,
surrounded by countless beauties.
Threaten him with me and an unborn child?
Don't you find that laughable?
You're a man of status.
Why not defeat him fair and square,
and forge your own legend?
Why resort to such despicable tactics?
It's absolutely pathetic.
You know nothing of how unfathomable
the Heir of the Wu Clan truly is.
Or understand
what a bloodline heir
truly means
to the Wu family.
I've had countless opportunities
to strike Wu Ming down,
but I held myself back every time.
Because I felt it wasn't certain enough.
This man, Wu Ming,
has erratic fortune,
with endless hidden cards up his sleeve.
If I can't manage
to kill him in one blow,
and sever all his chances of survival,
there will be endless trouble.
And you,
along with this child,
are the deadliest key to his fortress.
That's far more reliable
than acting on my own.
I don't understand your schemes,
but I understand human nature.
If this Ghost Needle is vital to you,
he absolutely will not trade it away.
Even if it were me,
I wouldn't make such a foolish choice.
You've miscalculated.
You're clever,
and tough.
Such a pity about that body of yours,
and your flesh and bone.
I don't like arrogant women.
Because that usually means
stupidity,
and not knowing one's place.
Guichen!
You sneaking, cowardly
rat who only schemes in the shadows!
If you've got the guts, just kill me!
Give me a quick end!
Wu Ming doesn't care about me at all.
He doesn't care about this child either.
You've miscalculated.
You old bastard!
Just go to hell!
Kill you?
Of course I'll kill you.
However,
first you must lure Wu Ming here.
I'll tear him to pieces,
and then, right before his eyes,
send you and your child to the afterlife.
That
is what I call perfection.
Kill me if you dare!
Just kill me!
Wu Ming.
Stay away!
Don't come!
Wu Ming.
You're a bit late.
Your wife and child are in grave danger.
If you don't save them now,
they'll be lost to you forever.
Wu Ming.
Did you really think
I'd let you save them so easily?
Yama's Ten Annihilations:
Descent of Yama!
Wu Ming.
We're nothing to each other.
You don't have to save me.
Even with this child,
you owe me nothing,
nor this child.
Just go.
Can't you hear what I'm saying?
I'm nothing to you.
You're the mother of my child.
The first woman I was ever intimate with.
For that alone,
I won't let anyone hurt you.